{
    "id": "51c0b3f9dcbf490399ef9e672abc06c9",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The killer smothered the victim ……………………… a pillow.",
            "description": "We use with to refer to the instrument used by somebody.",
            "answers": [
                "against",
                "with",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "433ac8c7f6b24c26944dd0d467324e44"
        },
        {
            "question": "You have an ink smudge ……………………….. your shirt.",
            "description": "We use on to indicate position on the surface of something.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c0f9e44c1ba24d43aeaa8c28a07c184e"
        },
        {
            "question": "She snapped ……………………….. me when I tried to comfort her.",
            "description": "The words snapped, yelled, shouted etc., are followed by at.",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9e24d8f1570c4bfbb67c7e3a86b50f6f"
        },
        {
            "question": "The professor was sparing ………………………… his praise.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "in",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "80ad971e64504f2a948fcb9a1ef0974e"
        },
        {
            "question": "He demonstrated a staunch belief …………………………… human rights.",
            "description": "Belief is followed by in.",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "with",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "4b5c5635d26c4c01afa6cbe96759372e"
        },
        {
            "question": "My feet ached …………………………… the two-hour stand.",
            "description": "From can indicate the cause. ",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "with",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7b9eb78f140a4c07a15437feb980e2e8"
        },
        {
            "question": "He stormed …………………………… the waiter and embarrassed everyone at the table.",
            "description": "We use at after some verbs to indicate the target. ",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "13c0364bf78b477386b83f630cddaaf8"
        },
        {
            "question": "I can’t believe you would stoop ……………………….. such nonsense.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "327579bd284e4a4c85f58d9bd55880b3"
        },
        {
            "question": "He struck me ………………………….. his fist.",
            "description": "We use with to refer to the instrument used by somebody.",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "by",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7ae0e5e7ad504d84b6c80a4ff160cdce"
        },
        {
            "question": "She stretched the clothesline …………………………. two trees.",
            "description": "Use between to speak of two things.",
            "answers": [
                "between",
                "among",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "20a3368a43e44cbfbbb657a5cf19ee25"
        },
        {
            "question": "The region has long been stricken ……………………………. poverty.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "from",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3f86a1508f394acab396484e270bf790"
        },
        {
            "question": "All hands were rescued ………………………….. the stricken ship.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "off",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "80bfce49a3b143149fb649a3ebc64534"
        }
    ]
}